quotev.com 2018-03-28

# Privacy

**Cookies and other tracking technologies**

>   
>  Some of our services utilize cookies and other tracking technologies. A cookie is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall information previously indicated by a user. Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet protocol addresses, browser and device types, clickstream patterns, and dates and times of access.
> 
> Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may choose to block cookies, but you will be unable to use parts of the services.
> 
> Third party vendors use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our services and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based ads by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

**Security**

>   
>  Wherever your personal information may be held within our services or on their behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the personal information from unauthorized access or disclosure.  
> 

**Third parties**

>   
>  We do not intend to transfer personal information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on our behalf, unless such transfer is either: legally required; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud or security issues; or to protect our rights or property.  
> 

**Transfer of assets**

>   
>  We may acquire or buy, be acquired, or merge with other businesses or assets. In such transactions, both personal and non-personal information will likely be one of the transferred assets.   
> 

**Links**

>   
>  These services contain links and other resources from third party sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.  
> 

**Children**

>   
>  We do not seek to collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. If any child provides us with personal information, a parent or guardian should contact us (using the pertinent "Report" link is recommended) and such information will be deleted from our records.  
>
